<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SectorSecured</string>
    <string name="level1_description">
        Welcome, Cipher. I am NULL, an insider within Enemy-Corp (E-Corp), the shadowy force manipulating Nexis from the shadows. I have chosen you as the guardian to liberate this city from their oppressive grasp.
        \n\nHowever, your journey begins with a challenge that tests your ingenuity. To unlock your mission, you must first discover the key that lies within. Sometimes, the answers you seek are hidden in plain sight.
        \n\nThe fate of Nexis hangs in the balance, and only your skills can tip the scales. Embrace the challenge that awaits you.
    </string>
    <string name="level2_description">
        Congratulations, Cipher. You\'ve completed your first test; now, can you discern what comes next?
        \n\nIn this next phase, you face a locked door with no input fields or buttons. Silence surrounds you, but there’s always a way to turn whispers into action.
        \n\nRemember, in the digital realm, every app has a path. Your knowledge of the system is your greatest ally.
        \n\nFind a method to navigate past this barrier and reveal what lies beyond. The secrets of E-Corp await.
    </string>
    <string name="level3_description">
        Cipher, E-Corp has concealed another clue within the fabric of this app. They trust that burying information in obscure places will keep it beyond reach.
        \n\nBut true mastery means uncovering what others overlook. Seek out the fragments woven into the code itself – a concealed message that only a vigilant mind can uncover. Follow this thread, and you’ll find the path forward.
    </string>
    <string name="level4_description">
        Cipher, we’ve gathered intel on a key player within E-Corp—"PhantomHack." He’s been feeding E-Corp crucial info. We’ve tracked his movements, but need to dig deeper.
        \n\nYour task: infiltrate the login system. There’s a vulnerability in how user data is handled, and PhantomHack’s credentials are within reach. Accessing his account will reveal what he’s been transmitting to E-Corp.
    </string>
    <string name="level5_description">Cipher, you’ve made a significant breakthrough—PhantomHack’s phone is now in your hands. With it, you’ve gained access to a wealth of information. But this is only the beginning.
        \n\nYou’re deep in the heart of enemy territory. Use your skills to uncover hidden hosts and confidential files—the secrets you uncover could change everything. Time is ticking, and E-Corp is always watching. Find what’s hidden, and expose the truth before it’s buried forever.
    </string>
    <string name="level6_description">
        Cipher, it’s confirmed—PhantomHack is working with E-Corp. We need to stay alert.
        \n\nI\'ve hidden a message in code for you to figure out. Can you find out what I’m saying through this encryption?
        \n\n(Fix the broken decryption algorithm)
    </string>
    <string name="protocol_passcode">fc7cdd1ed94bb07a2a52a3ef8da6c1ef1b11a2bb08988bb121e27bc82065b77f</string>
    <string name="final_task">Vavgvngr cebgbpby ‘Mreb Gehfg’—ab bar vf fnsr, rira gubfr pybfrfg.</string>
</resources>
